Four, 15, 15, 15, 20, 25, texting.
And we're going to the implication.
Five, six, far, bar key.
Good to know that.
Thank you.
I'm going to work.
We'll just ask that you give our council members wisdom and guidance.
They make a pledge to lead them to the flag of the United States of America.
And through the public, for which is France?
One nation, another guy.
We need to do this.
We need to do this tomorrow.
Four public input on to get the personal appearances.
Five, five minutes.
Motion to prove.
Second.
So, goal.
Five.
Four minutes.
Two minutes.
Five.
Five minutes.
For the April 1st, 2020, five regular meeting.
Motion to prove.
Second.
Five.
Four.
Two.
Five.
Six dollars, four dollars.
One second.
On rental services.
For lease and naturally.
Third.
plans.
ột.
Four thousand.
Four.
Thirty.
Four dollars.
Three.
Three years.
our color copy amount that we can have before we are charged overages, which should save us roughly
17 hundred a year as well.
Okay.
Second.
First, I don't want to talk.
Okay.
So the way that we do the agendas is kind of an antiquated system when they purchased, grandkids,
they purchased part one and part three, but they didn't purchase part two.
And so when we go in and upload all of the agendas, it takes hours to do that.
And so this software will allow the departments to assist in that process.
And then also we won't have the incentive that we have with their oxygen item when I did not include the PowerPoint.
With this software.
And I'm happy to answer any questions.
And also this was budgeted in the IT budget for the year.
Yes, it is.
Just make sure the board was aware of that, so.
I might want you to do.
Second.
Parker.
Sorry.
Jones.
Hi.
Other new business.
Any of which is for business that's close to the agenda.
10 staff reports.
15 announcements.
12 of this meeting will be continued from council chambers.
Read me in the staff and the purpose of executive session.
Have you questioned the agenda on number 18 as a regular meeting amongst the council?